{
    "subject": "resource/Richard_C._Mangam",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "United States Army Medal of Honor recipient",
    "human_readable": "Richard C. Mangam was a United States Army Medal of Honor recipient.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9725792407989502,
            "question": "When was Richard C. Mangam awarded the Medal of Honor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9513115286827087,
            "question": "What prestigious award did Richard C. Mangam receive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8783029317855835,
            "question": "Were there any other notable recipients of the Medal of Honor during Richard C. Mangam's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8645988702774048,
            "question": "Who was Richard C. Mangam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7564612627029419,
            "question": "What were some of Richard C. Mangam's accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6027258634567261,
            "question": "What is the Medal of Honor awarded for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5846786499023438,
            "question": "In what military branch did Richard C. Mangam serve?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4087357521057129,
            "question": "What conflicts did Richard C. Mangam participate in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3979496657848358,
            "question": "Is Richard C. Mangam still alive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3420364558696747,
            "question": "Can you find information about Richard C. Mangam's family?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Richard C. Mangam was a United States Army Medal of Honor recipient.",
            "html": "dbpedia_530_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Richard C. Mangam still alive?",
            "html": "dbpedia_530_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What conflicts did Richard C. Mangam participate in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_530_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what military branch did Richard C. Mangam serve?",
            "html": "dbpedia_530_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_530_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_530_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_530_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_530_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_530_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_530_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_530_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_530_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_530_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_530_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because, according to the documents provided, Richard Christopher Mangam was indeed a Private in the United States Army and received the Medal of Honor for his role in the American Civil War."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Richard Christopher Mangam, including his rank as a Private in the U.S. Army, his service in the 148th New York Infantry, and his Medal of Honor for capturing the flag of the 8th Mississippi Infantry at Hatcher's Run on April 2, 1865."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}